Rags is a tv movie, comedy, drama film directed by Bille Woodruff.
Rags follows the story of Charlie Prince, an orphan living with his acerbic and
unloving stepfather and spoiled, simple-minded stepbrothers.
Charlie's dream is to be a singer, and while he is vocally talented
and can write music, he can't seem to catch a break.
Kadee Worth, on the other hand, is the daughter of music mogul
Reginald Worth and is an international pop phenomenon.
While the world knows her as a glamorous superstar, she is secretly frustrated with
singing other people's songs and wearing clothes other people choose for her.
Kadee wants the world to hear and see her true talent.
Despite every obstacle that gets thrown in their way, once Charlie and Kadee find one another, they each
finally get what they have been looking for – a voice, a stage, an audience and each other.
Kadee Worth, played by Keke Palmer.
Charlie Prince, played by Max Schneider.
Reginald Worth, played by Isaiah Mustafa.
Finn, played by Avan Jogia.
Shawn, played by Drake Bell.
Lloyd McGowens, played by Burkely Duffield.
Rags is a Nickelodeon Original Movie.
It is a musical, gender-switched inversion and modernization of the Cinderella fairy tale,
starring Keke Palmer, Max Schneider, Drake Bell, Avan Jogia, and Nick Cannon.
The film premiered on Nickelodeon on May 28, 2012.
The film was released on DVD on August 28, 2012, as a
double feature with Big Time Movie.
The film explores themes of dreams, competition, musical, singer, teenager.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.